https://mentoringcomplete.com/privacy-policy

Mentoring UniversityAbout
Level up your mentoring.
Login
Mentoring Complete Privacy Policy
At Mentoring Complete, we’re committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy applies to our websites: Mentoringcomplete.comMentoringuniversity.comand Subscription Services and governs our data collection, processing, and usage practices. By using our Websites and Subscription Services, you consent to the data practices described in this Privacy Policy.If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Websites or Subscription Services.Note: We periodically update this Privacy Policy, so please occasionally check it for any revisions. If you have any questions regarding this policy, please don't hesitate to contact us. How our Subscription Service WorksWe use an online subscription service through HubSpot. To understand how HubSpot's subscription service works, we're quoting directly from HubSpot's privacy page regarding this matter:"Our online Subscription Service allows any company that uses it (our customers and HubSpot itself) to build marketing webpages on our servers where visitors can learn more about the company, download content, and provide their contact information and other demographic information. This information, which is stored and managed on our service providers' servers, is then used so that the visitors can be contacted about their interest in the company's goods or services and interact with the company. HubSpot provides the Subscription Service to our customers for their own marketing and lead generation, and we use it on our Websites for our own marketing and lead generation." – HubSpot privacy policyHubSpot's agreement with Management Mentors, Inc. prohibits us from using the Subscription Service to collect, manage, or process Sensitive Information. "Sensitive Information" refers to credit or debit card numbers, personal financial account information, Social Security numbers, Social Insurance numbers, passport numbers, driver's license numbers or similar personal identifiers, racial or ethnic origin, physical or mental health condition or information, or other financial or health information.NOTE: HubSpot is NOT responsible for the information we collect. In other words, if you have a problem with our Websites or Subscription Services, blame us, not HubSpot.Information We CollectWhile you don't need to provide any information in order to explore and enjoy our Websites, we do collect Navigational Information.In addition, we sometimes request that you provide Personal Information when you're seeking certain things from us (like our downloadable white papers, for example)."Navigational Information" refers to information about your computer and your visits to this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit, and pages viewed."Personal Information" refers to any information that you voluntarily submit to us and that identifies you personally, including contact information, such as your name, email address, company name, address, phone number, and other information about yourself or your business. Personal Information can also include information about any transactions, both free and paid, that you enter into via the Websites, and information about you that is publicly available on the Internet, such as from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and Google, or publicly available information that we acquire from service providers.Information about Children Our Websites and Subscription Services are not intended for or targeted at children under 13, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 13. If you believe that we have collected information about a child under 13, please contact us so that we may delete the information.How We Use Your Personal InformationWe never sell your personal information.We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party as an "easy" way to make money from your information. In other words, we won't sell your information to a company so that they can market to you.That said, if we (or our assets) are acquired by another company, whether by merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, or otherwise, that company would receive all information gathered by our Websites and the Subscription Services.We use your personal information to make your web experience better.In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Websites and to improve the Subscription Services with more targeted content.If you choose to download something from our site (or some similar action), you will need to provide, at the very least, an email address. We will use this email address to deliver the item you've asked for or to provide further directions on how to obtain it. You may receive further communications from Management Mentors, Inc. that we deem relevant to your business. That said, you are always in control and can unsubscribe yourself from these communications at any time by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of every email or contacting us via phone, email, snail mail, or through our contact page.At that point, we won't email you any further communications unless at some point you change your mind and you decide to provide your expressed consent. We do this for two reasons: first, it's just proper and polite, and, second, because we strive to be in compliance with the United States' CAN-SPAM Act.Your Opt-Out Rights Regarding Your Personal InformationIf you provide us with your Personal Information, you have the following rights with respect to that information:To review the user information that you have supplied to usTo request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to usTo request that your user information not be used to contact youTo request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we useTo request that your user information be deleted from our recordsTo exercise any of these rights, please contact us. We will promptly change, correct, or delete your information and notify you of the action we have taken.To Unsubscribe From Our CommunicationsYou may unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of our emails, by contacting us, or by clicking the link below. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their accounts.To Update Your Preferences Regarding Our CommunicationsTo view and update your preferences, including any lists you're subscribed to, simply click on the "email preferences" link at the bottom of every email.Who Has Access to Your Personal Information?Mentoring Complete by Engagedly Inc. employees have access to your personal information, and we also employ other companies and people to provide services (such as website development, for example) and they have access to your information, as well. These people understand that your Personal Information is confidential and can only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.On rare occasions, a trusted third party might ask us about the demographic makeup of our contact database. In these instances, we might provide statistical information about our database in aggregate, but never any information that could be used to identify any individual user.We Keep Your Personal Information SecureWe use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure.Retention of Personal InformationWe retain Personal Information that you provide us as long as we consider it potentially useful in contacting you about the Subscription Services or our other services, and then we securely delete the information. We will delete this information from the servers at an earlier date if you so request, as described in the opting out and unsubscribing sections above.International Transfer of InformationMentoring Complete by Engagedly Inc. is based in the United States, but we have serviced customers in other countries, as well. This Privacy Policy shall apply even if we transfer Personal Information to other countries.Important! Compelled DisclosureWe reserve the right to use or disclose your Personal Information if required by law or if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or to comply with a law, court order, or legal process.Your Personal Information and Social Media, External Websites, and Public ForumsSocial MediaOur Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.External WebsitesOur Websites occasionally provide links to other websites. We're not in control of these websites, so we're not responsible for the content and privacy practices of these websites. These links don't constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices.Public ForumsWe offer a public blog where people can leave comments. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose any information through this commenting function, this information may be collected and used by others. We will correct or delete any information you have posted on the Websites if you so request, as described in the opting out and unsubscribing sections above.How We Use Navigational Information The short of it goes like this: we use Navigational Information to operate and improve the Websites and the Subscription Services. Read below for nitty-gritty specifics.CookiesWe use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server.Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize pages on our Websites, or register for the Subscription Services, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits in what is referred to as "Smart Content." When you return to the same Website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the customized features.Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience interactive features on our Websites or Subscription Services. We keep track of pages you visit in order to determine the most popular or most used. This data is used to deliver better customized content and promotions.Log FilesWe may collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, Postal code, age, gender, preferences, interests, and favorites using log files that are not associated with your name or other personally identifying information.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that we automatically collect. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times, and referring website addresses. For these purposes, we do link this automatically-collected data to Personal Information, such as name, email address, address, and phone number.Third Party Tracking TechnologiesThe use of cookies (such as flash cookies) and web beacons by any tracking utility company is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these third party tracking technologies.If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please don't hesitate to contact us.
SOLUTIONS
Mentoring Complete
Precision Matching
Anytime Mentoring
Program Design and Implementation
MENTORING BENEFITS
Developing Talent
Diversity and Inclusion
Blog
People are at the heart of an organization's success. That's why Engagedly builds powerful, people-centric softwares so companies can buid happier workplaces. Today, Engagedly offers best-in-class performance management, employee engagement, and mentoring software.
Learn more about Engagedly.
Mentoring Complete by Engagedly Inc.
911 Washington Avenue,
St. Louis, MO, 63101,
© 2019 Mentoring Complete by Engagedly, Inc | Privacy Policy
| Mentoring Complete Login | Mentoring University Login
